<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sixty Days Six App Shipments Challenge on PB</title>
    <link>http://prashantb.com/tags/sixty-days-six-app-shipments-challenge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sixty Days Six App Shipments Challenge on PB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:27:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://prashantb.com/tags/sixty-days-six-app-shipments-challenge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making of my first Android App</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-07-01-making-of-my-first-android-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-07-01-making-of-my-first-android-app/</guid>
      <description>It is 11:30 in the morning, I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep the whole night. But, I am not sleepy. I am happy. I just finished with my first app of this vacation. I know I had taken the sixty days, six app shipments challenge but I am just finished with my first app, and it is already thirty days. More on it later.
Few FAQs on the app now.
Name of the app?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3, 4</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-07-day-3-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 00:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-07-day-3-4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-04-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-04-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Last day was not very productive. Downloaded Android SDK platforms for all the versions, was more than a GB in size and with my internet speed, it took me all night.
After the download was complete, setting up Android SDK was a real pain in the ass. Six months ago, I had so much trouble in setting it up in Windows, I thought Linux would be better, but it is as much pain as it was in Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-03-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-03-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I am two days late. But to be fair, I reached home just day before yesterday after a long 29 hours train journey. Also, I did not have a proper internet connection for the past two days. After a lot of brainstorming for ideas, I am finally starting work on one of the ideas. Not a great idea, but the main reason for working on it is, I will get to learn so much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Days, Six App Shipments Challenge</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-05-25-sixty-days-six-app-shipments-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-05-25-sixty-days-six-app-shipments-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Sixty days of summer. Sixty days of no college, no assignments, no studies. Sixty Days of learning and coding. What more can one ask for? :)
Since I am not doing any internship or any summer course, I have sixty days with me, and I can do anything I want to in these two months. Surely, not going to be lazying around. I won&amp;rsquo;t get this huge amount of free time again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>