<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Black Bile</title>
    <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Black Bile</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 02:11:18 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://prashantb.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting a Local Supermarket</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2018-10-13-visiting-a-local-supermarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 02:11:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2018-10-13-visiting-a-local-supermarket/</guid>
      <description>View this post on Instagram        weekend getaway #wanderlust #plasticbagpacker
A post shared by Prashant Baid (@prashantbaid) on Jun 11, 2018 at 11:52am PDT
 
It was Sunday and I woke up early in the morning. I went to the bathroom to brush my teeth. The mirror on top of my washbasin is a few inches below my eye level. I bent down a little to lean closer to the mirror.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attending a Fire Drill at Workplace</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2018-09-27-attending-a-fire-drill-at-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 23:21:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2018-09-27-attending-a-fire-drill-at-workplace/</guid>
      <description>It was five minutes to three. I was going for lunch. I normally eat much earlier. But my manager was late for his lunch today. I always go for lunch after the manager returns back from his lunch. With this convenient arrangement, we both get to see each other&amp;rsquo;s face less often.
The eating area was empty, there were only a couple of people in the room, both of whom were looking at their mobile screens, their thumbs positioned on the screen to make scrolling gestures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girl With A Pearl Earring</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2016-11-13-girl-with-a-pearl-earring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 17:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2016-11-13-girl-with-a-pearl-earring/</guid>
      <description>One day after I returned from work, I was browsing Reddit and Twitter as I usually do after coming back home. I saw a tweet of a painting. On other days I might have scrolled past it and moved on but on this occasion I found myself looking at this picture as if it had some spell on me. I could say it was because of the way her wide eyes looked at me, or the angle at which her face was turned, or her lips which were just slightly apart from each other and the earring she wore which was a distraction from her face, but in a pleasant way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book - The Catcher in the Rye</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2016-02-21-book-the-catcher-in-the-rye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 17:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2016-02-21-book-the-catcher-in-the-rye/</guid>
      <description>I recently read The Catcher in the Rye, written by J.D. Salinger. I follow a twitter handle that posts excerpts from J.D. Salinger’s works and that was a part of the reason why I wanted to read his works. So I started with the most famous of his works - The Catcher in the Rye. 

The Catcher in the Rye is a story about a teenager named Holden Caulfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>just another saturday at an engineering college</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-11-11-just-another-saturday-at-an-engineering-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 05:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-11-11-just-another-saturday-at-an-engineering-college/</guid>
      <description>Just another Saturday at an engineering college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web scraping websis portal to download the entire IT 7th semester data</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-07-22-web-scraping-websis-portal-to-download-the-entire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-07-22-web-scraping-websis-portal-to-download-the-entire/</guid>
      <description>Here is the final result in action: http://prashantb.com/itdata/
 I recently scraped websis manipal portal and downloaded their entire data for 7th semester IT students. I used this amazing simple_html_dom PHP library to get data. Web scraping with this PHP library is very easy but the problem arises when there is a login page in the way of your data. How do you bypass the login page? The goal is to log in to the websis portal, download all their data and save it in your local machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to run pointclub website locally</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-06-26-how-to-run-pointclub-website-locally/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-06-26-how-to-run-pointclub-website-locally/</guid>
      <description>To set up pointclub locally, you first need the code in your local machine. So to save all your files locally, you need to run the following command in your terminal-
git clone https://github.com/SciDevs/pointclub.git This may take a while.
After all the files have been downloaded, you are all ready to go. But you need to work with the dev branch, so to change the branch from master to dev, run the following command-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of the most amazing semester of college</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-05-24-end-of-the-most-amazing-semester-of-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 02:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-05-24-end-of-the-most-amazing-semester-of-college/</guid>
      <description>Three years ago, when I came to Manipal, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I really wanted to stay here. I am not very receptive to changes, especially when it comes to changes in the social environment. Unfortunately, social interaction is not my strongest quality. When it comes to building relationship with a person, it is a very long process for me, and I take a lot of time to reach that level where I can be comfortable around that person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>food diaries</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-05-24-food-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 00:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-05-24-food-diaries/</guid>
      <description>Food Diaries</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no title</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-03-17-it-has-been-a-while-since-i-last-blogged-a-couple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 13:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2013-03-17-it-has-been-a-while-since-i-last-blogged-a-couple/</guid>
      <description>It has been a while since I last blogged. A couple of weeks ago, I wrote a manipal version of facemash. It got a few lakh hits, and in the end I had to shut it down because a legal panel had been set up against me. That was a crazy week. Building your product and destroying it in the same week, cannot get more thrilling than that. And in the same week, some fun adventures like trekking, exploring places in manipal, some deep conversations with friends, it was the most happening week of this semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the food diaries</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-12-19-the-food-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-12-19-the-food-diaries/</guid>
      <description>Pan Fried Momos @ The Blue Poppy, Calcutta. June, 2012.White Sauce Pasta @ Chai Break, Calcutta. July, 2012.Chowmien @ Kalika Restaurant(roadside), Calcutta. June, 2012.Wheat Beer @ The Biere Club, Bangalore. December, 2012.Margherita Pizza @ Caffé Pascucci, Bangalore. December, 2012.Risotto @ Afraa, Calcutta. June, 2012.Jhaal Muri @ Paritosh&#39;s Place, Manipal. October, 2012.Draught Beer @ Afraa, Calcutta. July, 2012.Onion Uttapam @ Woodlands, Udupi. November, 2012.Chocolate Brownie @ Bliss, Bangalore. December, 2012.The Food Diaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 am writings - I</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-11-02-3-am-writings-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 03:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-11-02-3-am-writings-i/</guid>
      <description>Ever thought how it feels like when you want to write but you have nothing concrete going on in your mind and at the same time there are millions of things you are thinking, all simultaneously, disjointed yet mashed together, the summation of which is making no sense at all.
Exams, three in the night and and an excellent breezy weather outside, the combination of the three makes for an excellent time to write, think, dream, procrastinate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts about writing</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-08-19-thoughts-about-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 22:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-08-19-thoughts-about-writing/</guid>
      <description>I have had a blog since 2006. My first blog was a very cheesy blogspot where I used to write about hacking and related stuff. It was really stupid. And ever since, I knew writng wasn&amp;rsquo;t really my thing. I clearly don&amp;rsquo;t have any talent in writing. My vocabulary stopped growing when I was five and grammar hasn&amp;rsquo;t been very kind to me either. I really wish I could write well, play with words, come up with clever phrases and lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Friday evening..</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-07-27-on-a-friday-evening-for-most-of-us-you-sit-at/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-07-27-on-a-friday-evening-for-most-of-us-you-sit-at/</guid>
      <description>On a Friday evening (for most of us), you sit at your computer, with up to three of your closest friends nearby, when suddenly your Twitter stream starts flooding! Your IRC windows start flashing by! Your friends start clicking rapidly on their own machines! “It’s up!” one of them yells.
You have forty-eight hours, up to three friends, a shared Git repository, a remote server, and Rails (or your favorite Rack-based framework).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making of my first Android App</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-07-01-making-of-my-first-android-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-07-01-making-of-my-first-android-app/</guid>
      <description>It is 11:30 in the morning, I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep the whole night. But, I am not sleepy. I am happy. I just finished with my first app of this vacation. I know I had taken the sixty days, six app shipments challenge but I am just finished with my first app, and it is already thirty days. More on it later.
Few FAQs on the app now.
Name of the app?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3, 4</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-07-day-3-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 00:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-07-day-3-4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-04-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-04-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Last day was not very productive. Downloaded Android SDK platforms for all the versions, was more than a GB in size and with my internet speed, it took me all night.
After the download was complete, setting up Android SDK was a real pain in the ass. Six months ago, I had so much trouble in setting it up in Windows, I thought Linux would be better, but it is as much pain as it was in Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-03-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-06-03-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I am two days late. But to be fair, I reached home just day before yesterday after a long 29 hours train journey. Also, I did not have a proper internet connection for the past two days. After a lot of brainstorming for ideas, I am finally starting work on one of the ideas. Not a great idea, but the main reason for working on it is, I will get to learn so much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Days, Six App Shipments Challenge</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-05-25-sixty-days-six-app-shipments-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-05-25-sixty-days-six-app-shipments-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Sixty days of summer. Sixty days of no college, no assignments, no studies. Sixty Days of learning and coding. What more can one ask for? :)
Since I am not doing any internship or any summer course, I have sixty days with me, and I can do anything I want to in these two months. Surely, not going to be lazying around. I won&amp;rsquo;t get this huge amount of free time again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rahul Dravid, the childhood hero</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-03-09-rahul-dravid-the-childhood-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 23:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-03-09-rahul-dravid-the-childhood-hero/</guid>
      <description>When you are a kid, you are always asked by older folks, who do you want to be like, when you grow up? For me, it was always Rahul Dravid. My childhood was at the time when Rahul Dravid was it his peak; he was averaging more than 70 in tests and averaging more than 100 in the ones we won. It was the time when I was just developing interest in cricket, and when you begin watching some sport, you always root for someone, that is how you develop interest in a sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The problem with preconceived notions.</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-03-04-the-problem-with-preconceived-notions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 18:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-03-04-the-problem-with-preconceived-notions/</guid>
      <description>Humans are the most superior living creatures on earth. They have this amazing ability of making opinions about people just by looking at them. The way you dress, the way you talk, the way you comb your hair, your CGPA, and the place you come from is enough for people to make an opinion about you. Knowing the person is not a criteria here. We are humans. We are thinking creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can&#39;t always get what you want.</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-01-24-you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 23:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2012-01-24-you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t always get what you want. In fact, very seldom does everything go your way. Recently, I completed a web application. I was very optimistic about it. Worked really hard for it. Slogged for a lot of hours everyday. Woke up early on a Sunday, missed a brilliant Salim-Sulaiman concert. For what? To be told it can never be implemented. All the hours of hard work, all the hours spent on debugging, all in vain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no title</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-25-5827538993/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 12:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-25-5827538993/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s best?</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-25-but-who-can-say-whats-best-thats-why-you-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 12:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-25-but-who-can-say-whats-best-thats-why-you-need/</guid>
      <description>But who can say what’s best? That’s why you need to grab whatever chance you have of happiness where you find it, and not worry about other people too much. My experience tells me that we get no more than two or three such chances in a life time, and if we let them go, we regret it for the rest of our lives.&amp;#8212;Haruki Murakami (Norwegian Wood) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beautiful</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-22-beautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 05:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-22-beautiful/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>story of most of the people</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-21-story-of-most-of-the-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 02:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-21-story-of-most-of-the-people/</guid>
      <description>Story of most of the people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>facebook trolling :D</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-20-facebook-trolling-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 09:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-20-facebook-trolling-d/</guid>
      <description>Facebook trolling :D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>same feeling</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-20-same-feeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-20-same-feeling/</guid>
      <description>Same feeling ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ah those days</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-20-ah-those-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-20-ah-those-days/</guid>
      <description>Ah, those days !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i want this in my room</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-19-i-want-this-in-my-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 03:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-19-i-want-this-in-my-room/</guid>
      <description>I want this in my room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>current status want to go home</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-19-current-status-want-to-go-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 02:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-19-current-status-want-to-go-home/</guid>
      <description>Current Status: Want to go home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>solution problems in life</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-18-solution-problems-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-18-solution-problems-in-life/</guid>
      <description>Solution: Problems in Life. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bookmark</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-18-bookmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 12:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-18-bookmark/</guid>
      <description>Bookmark. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no title</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-16-5545709555/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 20:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-16-5545709555/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>greatest front page ever</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-07-greatest-front-page-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-07-greatest-front-page-ever/</guid>
      <description>Greatest. Front Page. Ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no title</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-04-5190574436/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-04-5190574436/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>current status</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-03-current-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 01:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-03-current-status/</guid>
      <description>Current Status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thermochromic urinal ah things that people</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-02-thermochromic-urinal-ah-things-that-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 21:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-02-thermochromic-urinal-ah-things-that-people/</guid>
      <description>Thermochromic Urinal. Ah, things that people make.
The truth is we’ve always enjoyed drawing stuff with pee. A gross use of body fluid, yes, but creativity has no bounds. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Tumblr and not Wordpress?</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-02-why-tumblr-and-not-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-02-why-tumblr-and-not-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Tumblr is not exactly a blogging platform. It is a microblogging platform with a social angle to it. As the name suggests, it is a tumblelog- a short-form blog. I can easily post text, pictures, videos, audios etc. And that completely serves my purpose of having a blog. Where tumblr really scores over wordpress is in the ease of use. I really love the tumblr UI. And in terms of user experience and user friendliness, tumblr is such a breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>current status</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-02-current-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 01:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-05-02-current-status/</guid>
      <description>Current Status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no title</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-30-what-a-rough-day-today-came-to-know-just-half/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 05:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-30-what-a-rough-day-today-came-to-know-just-half/</guid>
      <description>What a rough day today. Came to know just half an hour before a presentation that I am supposed to speak in that presentation. My biggest fear. Public speaking. And when I went there, stood up on the dice, i saw 80 students staring at me. I was unprepared. My heart pumped blood as fast as it could. And then I spoke. And what followed after that, I want to forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no title</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-27-4962293533/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 00:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-27-4962293533/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey reveals Mac and PC people think differently</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-27-survey-reveals-mac-and-pc-people-think-differently/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 00:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-27-survey-reveals-mac-and-pc-people-think-differently/</guid>
      <description>According to the results of a massive survey by Hunch.com,
 Mac people are frequently young, vegetarian city-dwellers who like modern art, liberal politics, and independent films. Meanwhile, Windows supporters tend to be older, more conservative, and more likely to compare talking about computers to &amp;ldquo;struggling with a foreign language.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>visualized ring around the world of data center</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-26-visualized-ring-around-the-world-of-data-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 23:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-26-visualized-ring-around-the-world-of-data-center/</guid>
      <description>Visualized: ring around the world of data center power usage (Source: Engadget)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now Watching - After Hours</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-22-now-watching-after-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-22-now-watching-after-hours/</guid>
      <description>Now Watching: After Hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now Watching - Adventureland</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-22-now-watching-adventureland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 02:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-22-now-watching-adventureland/</guid>
      <description>Now Watching: Adventureland</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now Watching - Fight Club</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-22-now-watching-fight-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 00:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-22-now-watching-fight-club/</guid>
      <description>Now Watching: Fight Club</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now Watching - A Few Good Men</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-21-now-watching-a-few-good-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-21-now-watching-a-few-good-men/</guid>
      <description>Now Watching: A few good men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now Watching - V for Vendetta</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-21-now-watching-v-for-vendetta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-21-now-watching-v-for-vendetta/</guid>
      <description>Now Watching: V for Vendetta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Jesus</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-15-current-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 01:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-15-current-song/</guid>
      <description>Current song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phone call v/s Email</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-15-phone-call-vs-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 01:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-15-phone-call-vs-email/</guid>
      <description>I believe the conversations over email or messages is better than the traditional phone calls. Or maybe, it is because i am a socially awkward introvert. But i just feel the quality of conversations over emails is better because of the simple reason that you get more time to think before you type something. Therefore, you are able to express your views better. And there is always an option to press the backspace button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>current status</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-14-current-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 00:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-14-current-status/</guid>
      <description>Current Status. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement</title>
      <link>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-11-i-secretly-love-the-early-stages-of-disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 13:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prashantb.com/posts/2011-04-11-i-secretly-love-the-early-stages-of-disagreement/</guid>
      <description>I secretly love the early stages of disagreement with a person I respect, because it means I&amp;rsquo;m about to learn something.&amp;#8212;@mrgan (twitter) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>